george paid for what he didto your father.
George为他对你父亲的所作所为 付出了代价
Bree confessed...
Bree的告白...
did you give zach moneyto go to utah?
是你给Zach钱赶他去犹他的？
Susan betrayed mike...
Susan对Mike的背叛...
what kind of friend is he?
他和你什么关系？
The real good kind.
非常要好
Andrew pushed the boundaries...
Andrew的挑舋...
zach's come home.Is there anything I can do?
Zach回来了 有什么需要我的吗？
Paul put his foot down...
Paul的强硬...
you can leave us alone.
你最好别管我们的事
So when do I tell peopleyou'll be back?
那你什么时候回来？
Couple,maybe three days.
两天,也许三天
And a stranger finally caught up with caleb.
"陌生人"的步步逼近
kisses are such simple things,
接吻在我们周遭司空见惯
we hardly notice them.
于是很少有人在意
But if we paid more attention,
we'd see that each kiss conveys a meaning all its own.
我们会发现不同的吻蕴藏着不同的含义
For example,
比如
some can say,"I'm so happy to see you."
有的代表着,"真高兴见到你."
Or,"I didn't realize you'd be here."
或者,"没想到你也来了"
Bye.
拜
Or,"honey,it's time to stop drinking."
抑或."亲爱的,不能再喝了."
The trick is in knowing how to tell the difference.
诀窍就在于懂得如何分辨它们
So I finally said,if I'm head cheerleader,
于是我宣布,如果我是啦啦队长
then nobodywears panties.
所有队员放"空档"
Yeah!
耶！
I just want you to knowas a former member
如果回到高中我还是步操队员的话
of my high school marching band,I would've appreciated that.
一定乐得美滋滋的
Wait a second,you were a bandgeek?
慢着,你以前爱玩乐团？
Oh,I don't believe it.
我才不信
What did you play?
你玩什么?
He played the tuba.I have pictures.
他玩大号,有照片为证
The tuba,huh?
大号,哈？
Yeah,go ahead,come on,comeon, get your licks in,go ahead.
耶,继续,继续,你接着讲
No,no,not at all.As a matter of fact,
不不,实际上
all of my secret crusheswere on the band geeks.
以前我暗恋的对象都是玩乐团的人
Come on,I know you cheerleader types.
别这样,我知道你是那种女孩
You wouldn't have said "boo"to guys like me.
你才不会像我这样的家伙叫好
No,you were more interestedin the guys like--like this.Now,
能引起你兴趣的家伙应该像这样,这样
I take ityou didn't play the tuba.
我猜你没玩过大号
No,I didn'T.
对,我没有
All I know is,I was a lonely,insecure tuba player.
我只知道,我是个孤僻 缺乏安全感的大号手
Girls like gabrielle would justrip my heart out.
像Gabrielle这样的女孩 只会让我伤心欲绝
Aw.
Aw
I didn't even had my first kissuntil I was 18.
我的初吻是在18岁
-18?
Pathetic,I know.
值得同情
Poor baby.I would've kissed you.
真可怜,我肯定会吻你
No,you wouldn't have.Yes,I would have.
不,你不会 谁说的,当然会
No,you wouldn't have.And it's okay,gaby.
不,你绝对不会 没关系,Gaby
Those scars healeda long time ago.
那些伤心事早已成为过去
Oh,for god sakes,come here.
看在上帝的份上,来
Now on behalf of allthe cheerleaders in the world,
代表全世界所有啦啦队长
forgive us.
原谅我们
Oh,yeah!Whoo!
噢,耶！
Yes,kisses mean different things to different people.
接吻因人而异
Ultimately,the meaning depends
最终,它究竟意味着什么
on the one who does the kissing...
全在乎当事人...
wowie.
哇
cheers.
干杯
And the who sees it happen.
和旁观者的感受
www.ydy.com/bbs Proudly Presents
-=伊甸园美剧 http://sfile.ydy.com=- 荣誉出品 本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业途径
Sync: YTET-gagegao -==www.ydy.com/bbs==-
-=YTET-伊甸园字幕组=- 翻译: 午夜飞行，princeblue 保罗，Noemie，maggiezl
Desperate Housewives Season 02 Episode 01
-=YTET-伊甸园字幕组=- 校对: dene 时间轴:gagegao
after every party
每到派对结束
comes the time for cleaning.
开始清理打扫
We attend to the champagne
我们常常会发现
that was spilled,
香槟酒洒了
the knickknacks that got broken,
小玩意碎了
the food that went uneaten.
食物被剩了
Oh,here, let me take that.
这里，我来拿
And whatever other messes need cleaning up.
无论还有什么 都需要清算
So,uh,gaby...
那么,呃,gaby...
you know that thing
你知道
you and tom did tonight?
你和Tom今晚的即兴表演
The--the kiss?
那一吻？
Was that hysterical?
是不是激情四溢？
The look on tom's face!
看Tom的脸色！
Yeah.
耶
I know this sounds silly,
我知道这听起来有点傻
but...
但...
it kind of bugged me.
我有点难以释怀
You're not serious.
你不是说真的
Yeah,I am.
我是的
I don't--
我不想--
I don't want to make a big deal out of it,
不想小题大做
but,uh,
但是
could you maybe
你以后能不能
not do that again?
别再那样做？
Okay.
好吧
Thanks.
多谢
Okay.
好吧
Hey,what happened to the applewhites?
Applewhite一家子怎么搞得？
I thought you were gonna invite them.
我以为你邀请了他们
I did. Betty never R.S.V.P.'D.
我请了， Betty从来没理睬过
What do you guys think about the applewhites?
你们觉得Applewhite一家怎么样？
I like 'em,very nice.
我喜欢他们,非常友善
Very...
非常...
interesting.
有意思
Right,interesting.
没错,有意思
Hmm,they weird me out,too.
我对他们也挺好奇的
well,that's not what we're saying.
我们不是这个意思
not exactly,anyway.
不确切
You know, we were just having fun,
我们刚才只是
entertaining the crowd.
为了让大家开心
Oh,sure,but...
当然,但...
but maybe next time you could try juggling instead.
也许下次你变变戏法就成
What's going on?
怎么回事？
Nothing.
没什么
Really?
真的？
I sense a little tension.
我感到一丁点火药味
No,no tension.
不,没有火药味
What?
什么？
You make it sound like...
你说得就像...
I was making a pass at your husband.
我刚才在和你丈夫调情
And that's just a little bit insulting.
有点不尊重人的意思
I just said it bugged me.
我只是说有点困扰我
Why is that a problem?
那也有什么不对吗？
Is this about that kiss?
是关于那个吻？
What kiss?
什么吻？
Oh,you were in the living room.
你当时在起居房
Gaby planted a big,wet kiss
Gaby和Tom激情湿吻
on tom... as a joke.
不过只当玩笑
It was hilarious.
真是过瘾
You see?
你听见没？
Yeah,but to be fair to lynette,
对lynette公平点
you are an ex-model.
你是模特出身
And surely it must have dawned on you that some women
你应该明白有些女人会有意见
might prefer it if you didn't kiss their husbands.
如果你亲吻他们的丈夫
That's all I'm saying.
我就这意思
Oh,you guys, we're all friends.
我们都是朋友
This isn't something to get worked up over.
不值得为这些事闹不愉快
I'm not worked up.
我没有不愉快
Me neither.
我也没有
Hey,everyone,
大伙
did you see what kathy lewis was wearing tonight?
你们注意到Kathy Lewis 今晚穿的什么没？
And whoever told her that she could get away
不管是谁告诉她适合穿直条
with those vertical stripes should be shot.
应该被枪毙
Oh.
噢
Bye,sweetie.
再见，亲爱的
Zach is back!
Zach回来了！
Yeah,yeah,I know.
耶耶,我知道
You do?
你知道？
Yeah,he's been back for a couple of days now.
他已经回来好几天了
Well,that's great,isn't it?
那就太好了,不是吗？
Yeah.
是的
I thought you'd be happy about it.
我以为这会让你高兴
I thought that's what you wanted.
我以为这就是你想要的
I was hoping that I'd slowly establish
我打算和zach
a relationship with zach
慢慢相处
and then when we were comfortable,
当我们适应对方后
I'd tell him I was his real dad.
再告诉他我是他的生父
But now paul's back.
但现在Paul也回来了
And he doesn't want you anywhere near him.
他不让你接近他
He's threatened to tell the police
他威胁说要向警察说出
everything that happened in the desert--
沙漠里发生的一切
that I held a gun to his head.
我用枪指着他的头
Well,it's your word against his.
怎能听他一面之辞
But he doesn't have a record,and I do.
但他没有前科,我有
You know,despite what I did--
尽管我曾经...
sending zach away,
送走zach
I want you two to connect.
我真心希望你们能团聚
I hope you know that.
我希望你明白
I do.
我明白
And on the bright side,
往好的方面想
I don't have to wonder where he is anymore.
我也不必再为他的处境担心
It says that you can do a report on anything
上面说你可以任选一本指定书目
from the suggested reading list,
写报告
which includes "the old man and the sea,"
包括《老人与海》
"the pearl,"
《珍珠》
"much ado about nothing."
《无事生非》
That sounds good. What do you like?
听起来不错,你喜欢哪个
I don't care.
我无所谓
Let's start with "the pearl."
从《珍珠》开始吧
It's got a sad ending,but it's good.
结局有点悲伤,但是本好书
We'll start with that.
我们从那开始
You know,
你知道
it's not gonna be so bad.
也没有那么糟糕
but maybe next time you could try
Okay,
好吧
I know this isn't what you want.
我知道这你不乐意
But I need to keep you close to me
但我必须把你看好
just for a while.
暂时而已
There are peoplein this neighborhood
这周围有些人
who aren't thrilledthat we're back.
不太乐意我们回来
People I don't trust.
我不信任的人
People like...mike delfino?
就像Delfino？
Why would yousay that?
你这话什么意思？
When you disappeared,
你失踪那段时间
mrs. Tillman said that miketook you somewhere to kill you.
Tillman夫人说是Mike 把你抓走并要杀了你
That's ridiculous.Why would mike wanna kill me?
真荒唐,Mike为什么要杀了我？
Because you murderedmrs. Huber?
因为你杀死了Huber夫人？
What did you say?
你说什么？
Well,mrs. Tillman said thatyou murdered mrs. Huber
Tillman说你杀了Huber夫人
because she wasblackmailing mom.
是因为她当初在勒索妈
And you believed her?
你相信她？
No,not exactly.
不确定
I mean,why? Should I?
为什么？我该不该？
Zach,you know me
Zach,你了解我
Better than anyone.
比谁都了解
Do you honestly believe that I am capableof murder?
你真的相信我会干出杀人的勾当？
No.
不
All right,then.
那就对了
Of course...
当然...
I didn't think mom was capableof suicide,either.
我也没想到妈会自杀
On second thought,
重新考虑过
why don't we start with"much ado about nothing"?
我们为什么不从《无事生非》开始
I think we could usea few laughs around here.
我想我们需要寻找些笑料
Yeah,man...
是的,伙计..
yeah,he sure is.I just...
他绝对是,我只是...
-probably.
-也许
Yeah.
对
hey.
嘿
Get over here. Now.
给我过来
Somebody's angry.
有人生气了
Did oneof your souffls fall?
你做的小点心掉地上了？
I saw what you didwith your friend.
我看到你和你朋友在干些什么
Oh,and you didn't turn intoa pillar of salt. Good for you.
你居然没有暴跳如雷.真有你的
This is not a joke,andrew.
这不是开玩笑,Andrew
What if the neighborshad seen you?
要是邻居看见怎么办？
Well,I'd hope they'd thinkthat I'd landed a hottie.
我只希望他们会觉得我有点火辣
I may not be able to control
我也许控制不了
what you do outsideof this home,
你在外面的所作所为
but whileyou are under this roof,
但当你还在这屋檐下
you will not mockmy values.
不允许你有辱我的声誉
If you so muchas smile at that boy,
如果你不尽快和他断绝来往
so help me,I will ship you offto camp hennessey
真是帮我个大忙 我就直接送你去Hennessey
and I will not pick you upagain until you are 18.
到你18岁之前休想我再来接你回家
Do I make myself clear?
听清楚没有？
Aren't you forgettingsomething?
你是不是忘了什么？
I know you like to knocka few back before bedtime.
我知道你睡觉前喜欢喝两口
Go on,take it. It's okay.
拿上,没关系
We both knowthat of the two of us,
我们都知道我们两人中间
I'm the onethat doesn't judge.
只有我不会指手画脚
Please. I don't wannastay down here.
求你了，我不想留在下面
I-I know.
我了解
I'm sorry,K.
不好意思，K
I'm sorry.
不好意思
Matthew,I think we mighthave termites.
Matthew 房子可能有白蚁了
You need to takea look at those steps
在阶梯折断我们脖子之前
before one of usbreaks our neck.
你要维修一下了
What's the matter?Is your brother okay?
怎么了，你哥哥好吗
No,he's not.He hates it down here.
不，他讨厌待在下面
He wants to be with us.You're being cruel.
他想和我们在一起 你太残忍了
If you are so concernedabout him,
如果你真的关心他
you should spend less timeon your computer
你就应该少玩电脑
and more time down herekeeping him company.
多来陪他
We're bringing him up,
我们会让他出来
but not until I am surethat it's safe.
但要在安全的情况下
hey,you!
喂，你！
yeah?
什么事？
What's the deal?
你呆在这干嘛？
You've been parked on our streetfor two hours.
你的车已经在 我们的街上停了2个小时了
Oh,I'm doinga property appraisal.
噢，我正在做财产评估
Some neighbors of yoursare thinking about moving.
你的一些邻居正在考虑搬走
The applewhites?
AppleWhite 他们家？
I'm not reallyallowed to say.
我真的不能透露
I sold them that house.You know,this is my turf!
那套房子是我卖给他们的 你要知道，这里是我的地盘
Who do you work for?
你为谁干活？
Geist realty?
Geist 房产公司？
Ah,westside properties.
啊，Westside 物产公司
Yeah,well,whoever it is,you go back
但不管他是谁 你回去告诉你的老板
and you tell your bossesthat nobody, and I mean,nobody,
没有人，我是说
buys or sells propertiesin this neighborhood
没有人能够在这片区域买卖房产
without going throughedie britt,you got that?
而不通过Edie Britt的手
Look,lady,I just gowhere I'm told.
是这样，夫人 我只是去我被要求去的地方
You look,you cross me,
听着，你要是想找我的麻烦
and I will beyour worst nightmare.
我将成为你最恐怖的恶梦
I'm a dangerous woman.You don't wanna mess with me.
我是一个危险的女人 不要惹我
You got it.
知道了
Ms. Mayer?
Mayer 夫人
Zach.May I talk to you?
Zach,我能和您说两句话吗？
I have some thingsthat I need to say.
有些事我需要说出来
Okay.
行
I-I know that I dida lot of bad stuff--
我，我知道我做了些很坏的事--
stuff that I'm not gonnabe able to take back.
我是无法将其挽回的
Ms. Mayer,I'm--I'm really sorry.
Mayer 夫人，我，我真的很抱歉
But when I was livingon the streets,you know,
但是当我住在这条街上，你知道
I had a lot of time to--to just sit and think to myself
我有许多时间去坐下来
and clear my head and...
思考我自己和总结一下
I've grown up,you know?I don't want you to worry.
我已经长大了，你知道吗？ 我不想你去担心
I'm not gonna bebothering you anymore.
我将再也不会打扰你们了
Either of you.
你们每一个人
Well,thanks.We appreciate that.
谢谢，我们很感激
Please don't tell my dadthat I talked to you.
请不要告诉我爸爸我和你们说过这些
He's just--he's been really...
他最近真的有些...
intense lately.
太紧张了
Well,what do you think?
嗯，你怎么看？
He seems different.
他似乎变了
I believe him.
我相信他
Yeah,I can't believeI'm about to say this,
是呀，我刚要说我没法相信
but I feel sorry for him.
但是我觉得对他很难过
It's likehe's so fragile.
似乎他是那么脆弱
I know,and he's locked in thathouse with mr. Creepy 24/7.
我知道 并且他被和可怕先生关在一个屋檐下
Did you know that he'shomeschooling zach now?
你知道他现在要给Zach上家教吗？
I think he shouldspend some time
我认为他应该花些时间
with a decent role model,don't you?
与一个有教养的人呆在一起 你不认为吗？
Hi!
嗨！
Hey,you're out early.
嗨，你今天出门挺早
Oh,I just wanted to pick up
对呀，我正打算去拿
some fresh croissantsfor breakfast.
一些新鲜的新月面包当早餐
Oh,cool. Listen,I just wanted you to know
很不错，我想让你知道
I appreciated youbacking me up last night,
我十分感激你昨晚站在我这一边
you know,with the kiss thing.
你知道，是接吻那件事
To be honest,I don't thinkI would've liked it,either.
坦率地说 我也不认为我会喜欢那样的事
Yeah,but I probablyshould've just gone with it.
是呀，但我也许应该这事就那么过去
Gaby was just being gaby--having fun.
Gaby 就是那样的人，爱闹
No,I wouldn't be so hardon yourself, given her history.
不，我不会象你那样想 考虑到她的过去
What do you mean?
你是指什么？
You know,the affair.
你知道，外遇的事
Gaby had an affair?
Gaby 有过外遇？
-You didn't know?
-你不知道？
No!
不知道！
I thought everybody knew.
我以为每个人都知道了
Oh,I feel awful.
噢，我觉得自己很糟糕
Oh,ida greenberg'sbehind you.
噢，Ida Greenberg 在你后面
Ida,just a second.
Ida，稍等一下
I am stunned.
我太吃惊了
Who was it with?
和谁有一腿？
I shouldn'thave said anything.
我不应该说任何事的
Bree,come on,just tell me.
Bree，拜托，就告诉我
her gardener.
她的园丁
Oh,you're kidding!
噢，你一定在开玩笑！
No,no,not him.Helen rowland's son,john.
不，不，不是他 Helen Rowland 的儿子，John
The teenager?
那个未成年人？
ida,wait,or go around!
Ida，稍等一下，要不就绕过去！
Does gaby knowthat you know?
Gaby 知道你知道这事么？
Absolutely not.
肯定不知道
I thinkthe best thing to do
我想最好的事就是
is just smile and pretendyou don't know anything.
保持微笑然后装作什么事你都不知道
Hi.
嗨
Oh,sorry!
噢，对不起！
Are you okay?
你还好吗？
Yeah.
是的
I'm all right.
我还行
What's up?
什么事？
We have an idea how to bringyou and zach together.
我们想了个使你和zach聚会的点子
Bowling.
打保龄
-Bowling?
- 打保龄？
Yeah,I e-mailed zach,
是的 我已经给zach发电子邮件了
and he said he's gonna meetus there.
他说他会去的
You can come,too.
你也可以过来.
Does paul knowabout this?
paul知道这件事么？
No,and we're not planningon telling him.
不 我们不打算告诉他
I don't thinkthat's a good idea,susan.
susan 我不认为这是个好主意
Mike,I'm part of the reasonthings got so screwed up.
mike 事情搞到这地步我也有责任
I just want a chanceto make things right.
我只是想做点什么
And you're okay with this--being around zach?
你不介意么---和zach呆在一起？
We talked to him.He's changed.
我们和他谈过了 他有所改变
Well,I guesswe're going bowling.
好吧 那就这么定了 打保龄
Wake up,sleepyhead.
醒醒 懒猪
I brought fresh croissantsfor breakfast!
我买了新鲜的新月面包！
uh,hi,mrs. Van de kamp.
啊 嗨 van de kamp夫人
I'm justin,andrew's lab partner...
我叫justin 是andrew的实验室拍档
from school.
学校里的...
Dude,wake up.
伙计 醒醒
Andrew...
I want you downstairs... now.
我要你马上下楼来 马上
Okay,first of all,I want youto march back upstairs
好吧 首先 我要你回到楼上
and tell your friend he isno longer welcome in this house.
告诉你的朋友再也不要到我们家来了
But we haven't even had breakfast yet!
但我们早饭都没吃呢
I am serious,andrew.
我是认真的 andrew
You tell himto get out of here this second
你告诉他马上离开这里
or I will call the police,
否则我就报警
and I will have him removed!
我还会让他走
Well,go ahead,call 'em.
好啊 报警吧
Oh,you think I won't?
你认为我不敢？
I just wonderhow they'll react
我只是在想他们发现你就是杀害
when they find out thatyou killed george williams.
george williams的凶手时 会有何反应
I didn't kill george.
我没杀george
Well,no,but you sat thereand let him die,
是啊 但是你坐在那里看他死去而不管
which,I'm no lawyer,but I'm pretty sure
我不是律师 但我确信
there's a crimein there somewhere.
这种行为多少有些犯罪的成分
Andrew...
don't get me wrong.I mean,I'm glad you did it.
别误会 你那么做我很高兴
But when the cops get here,my official position will be,
但警察来了的话 我的立场会是
uh,"oh,my god,I'm beingraised by a homicidal maniac."
噢 "啊 天哪 我被一个杀人狂抚养着"
I think I might eventhrow in a few tears.
我可能还会流几滴眼泪的
You would actuallylet the police
你真的会让警察
arrest your own mother?
逮捕你的妈妈？
Hey,we all gotta cutthe apron strings at some point.
嗨 我们彼此彼此啊
Come on,penny. Let's getthose groceries in there.
来吧 penny 我们把东西搬回家
Come on. Here we go.Get this one...
来吧 走了 拿住这个..
and this one,and daddy--uh-oh! Whoa!
还有这个 噢
oh!
噢
Oh,it looks likeyou could use a hand.
噢 看来需要帮忙啊
Bless you. Here,gaby.
谢谢你 gaby 给
And penny!
还有 penny
Oh,come here,you sweet little thing.
噢 过来 可爱的小东西
Well,thank you so much,gaby.Come on in.
gaby 真是太感谢了 请进
Oh,god,um,tom?
哦 天哪 嗯 tom?
Yeah?
怎么了？
Uh,I thinkshe got sick.
呃 我认为她吐了
Oh,I'm so sorry.
哦？很抱歉
Usually,she only throws upon immediate family.
通常她只会吐在直系亲属身上
I'm honored.
我很荣幸
oh,um,do you mind just puttingher in the playpen there?
噢 嗯 你可以把她先放到婴儿床上
hello.
你好
Guess what? Ed loved the pitch.I got off early!
你猜怎么着？ed 喜欢这个 我今天可以早下班
You're kidding! That's great!
开玩笑吧 太好了
Hey,I'm rightby the supermarket.
嗨 我正在超市里
You want me to pick up anything?
你有什么要捎的么？
Um,actually,I just came from there.
嗯 其实我刚从那回来
Except,you know what?I forgot bread.
不过 我忘了买面包了
-Would you mind?
-你介意捎点么？
Not at all.
不
Tom,I need to wipe up.Do you have a towel?
tom 我要擦干 你有毛巾么 ？
Sure,hold on.
当然了 等会
Hey!
嗨
Hey,honey.
嗨 亲爱的
Hey,did you get the bread?
嗨 你买面包了么？
Oh,yeah,they were out.
哦 那个啊  他们卖光了
Of bread?
面包？
Yeah. Hey,gaby.
是的 嗨 gaby
A surprise seeing you here.
真是稀客啊
Well,I saw that tomwas overwhelmed,
我看到tom拿不了
so I thoughtI'd give him a hand.
所以我帮帮忙
Really?Wow,that was nice of you.
是么？哇 你可真是太好了
Is there a problem?
有什么问题么？
No.
没有
Really?
真的么？
Because I sensethat you're annoyed
我觉得你对我在你出去的时候
you found me here whenyou weren't home. Am I wrong?
到访很不高兴 是我误会了么？
Lynette?
Okay. yeah.
好吧  是的
So exactly what are youdoing here helping out?
那么你到底在这帮了什么呢？
Damn it,lynette,if thishas to do with that stupid kiss
该死 lynette 还是关于昨天晚上
the other night,I'm gonna lose it!
那个吻的话 我可真受够了
Whoa,whoa,whoa,what's going on?
哇 哇 哇 怎么了这是
Lynette thinks I was hittingon you at bree's party.
lynette认为我在bree的晚会上勾搭你
that's ridiculous.
这太荒谬了
I never said that.
我从没这么说
What I said was that it made me uncomfortable
我说的是你吻他
when you kissed him.
使我很不舒服
It's obviouslyan issue for me.
我很介意
And yet,here you are,alone inmy kitchen with my husband.
而你这时又和 我丈夫单独呆在我家厨房
So you tell me,are you hitting on him?
你说,你有没有勾搭他？
Lynette.
I can't believe you.I have done nothing
你怎么了 我做了什么错事
to deserve this kindof mistrust.
使的你这么不信任我
Well,that's not entirely true.
好像不是什么都没有啊
What does that mean?
你什么意思
Come on,gaby.
别这样,gaby.
It's a small town. People talk.
唉呀 这是个小镇 大家爱嚼舌头
Okay,what's going on here?
噢 到底怎么回事？
I'll tell you.
我告诉你吧
Your wife doesn't trust mearound you
你老婆不放心我在你周围
because I had an affairwith my teenage gardener.
因为我曾和未成年园丁有过一腿
Oh.
噢
So I know susan mayerwould never tell.
susan mayer不会说的
It must've beenhelen rowland.
一定是helen rowland
She probably blabbedto all the girls at the salon.
她在美容院和那些个女人嚼舌头
And ida greenberggoes to that salon.
而且ida greenberg也去那
So if ida knows,the whole town knows.
所以ida知道的话，全城都知道了
And we're just gonna have tomove. That's all there is to it.
那我们需要搬家了 就是这样
Carlos,can you stop puttingfor two seconds
carlos 你能停会吗
and show me some support?
给我点支持
What do you expect me to do?You brought this on yourself.
要我做什么 你自己提起的
It wasa harmless little kiss!
只是个无伤大雅的吻
Why is everybody makinga big deal about this?
为什么大家都当会事
Because you had an affairwith an underage gardener.
因为你和未成年园丁上过床
People don't thinkyou're harmless.
人们认为你是威胁
They see you as a predator.
他们知道你不是吃素的
You're enjoying this,aren't you?
你在得意，是吧？
Punishing me,danglingthe affair over my head?
惩罚我，不时提起外遇
Well,I won't tolerate it.
我不会忍着的
Really?
真的？
So just what are yougonna do about it?
那想怎么办？
I'm gonna let youeven the score.
我要让你打平比分
Carlos,go have an affair.
Carlos,去搞婚外情吧
What?
什么?
I hadmy little indiscretion.
我自己做了一点轻率的举动
So you go have yours.Get it out of your system.
所以你也应该做一点 摆脱你常规的生活
-I know you want to.
- 我知道你想做
I do not.
我不想
Sure you do.Knock yourself out.
你当然想 疯狂一点
Call up an old college flame.Rent a call girl.
打电话给你以前大学的旧情人 或找个应召女郎
Fly to africa
或飞去非洲
and nail that little nunyou've been drooling over.
缠着那个你在梦里想念的可爱小修女
I don't care!
我不在乎
You're crazy.
你疯了
No,I'm pragmatic.
不，我很现实
Because onceyou finish your fling,
因为一旦你的冲动行为结束了
we'll be equals again.
我们就又平等了
And then you won'tbe able to judge me.
你也就不能再这样指责我了
And we cango back to being
然后我们就又能变成一对
a boring,averagemarried couple.
平淡，普通的夫妻了
Oh,just do me a favor.Don't bring back any diseases.
Oh, 只要帮我一个忙 不要带回来任何病菌
Are you sure you're notoverreacting
你真的确定你对 关于gabrielle的这整件事情
to this wholegabrielle thing?
没有反应过度吗?
Maybe.
也许吧
Yes.
是有一点过度
But gaby doesn't thinkshe did anything wrong.
但gaby不认为她有什么地方不对
That's not right,either.
这同样也是不对的
I guess.
可能吧
You'rean attractive man.
你是一个有魅力的男人
There is a primal need fora woman to protect what is hers.
一个女人去保护属于 她自己的东西是十分必要的
My initial impulsewas justified.
我最初的动机是正确的
So you really thinkshe's into me?
那么你真的认为她对我感兴趣?
I don't know.
我不确定
Because you're right.I am an attractive man.
你是对的 我确实是一个有魅力的男人
You know what?I've never told you this,
知道吗?我从来没有对你说起过这个
but sometimes when I bend downto pick up the morning paper,
但有时当我弯腰拿早报时
I catch bree van de kampchecking me out.
我发现bree van de kamp 在对我抛魅眼
You're kidding.
你开玩笑吧
No,scout's honor.
不，绝对真实
I've always exuded a certain sexual magnetism,
我总是散发出一种性感的吸引力
and as I get older,
随着我岁数的增加
I think it's onlybecoming more intense.
我想那只会变得更强烈
Are you drunk?
你喝醉了吗?
Oh,I'm a hot guyliving in a neighborhood
oh,我是一个住在到处都是
filled with nothingbut lonely ladies.
寂寞女人的社区里的性感男人
Oh.
They can't help themselves.I'm like... catnip.
她们控制不住自己 我就像是...猫薄荷花
Come here.
过来
What was that for?
这是什么意思?
Thank you.Thank you for reminding me
谢谢你，谢谢你提醒我
that I am the only womanin the whole world
我是这整个世界上唯一的
who could lovean idiot like you.
会爱上你这样一个傻瓜的女人
-I'll talk to gaby.
- 我会和gaby谈谈
I'm telling you,
我告诉你
-these women want me.
- 这些女人对我感兴趣
Oh,yeah.
oh,是啊
They see the rippling musclesunderneath this t-shirt...
她们看见了这件T恤下起伏性感的肌肉
good night,tom.
晚安，tom
They cannot resist me.
她们抗拒不了我
Shut up and go to sleep.
闭上你的嘴，睡觉
aah!
啊
son of a bitch.
该死的
you gotta be kidding me.
我简直不能相信
Whoa,whoa.
噢，噢
I'm here to help you,caleb.
我是来帮你的, caleb
All right?
可以吗?
Mama's gon' be mad.
妈妈会发疯的
Don't you worryabout that.
你不用担心那个
Moms love me.
妈妈们都很喜欢我
All right,let's go.
好了，我们走
No!
不
Okay,I'm sorry. I shouldn'thave talked to you like that.
好吧，我很抱歉 我不应该那样对你说话
Let's start over.
我们重新来过
Aah!
啊
Let's go.
我们走
I'm warning you,pinhead,
我警告过你，小东西
don't you make mecome down there after you.
不要让我下来抓你
Come on.
快点
Come on!
All right,you asked for it.
好吧，你自找的
I'm gonna beat the stupidright out of you.
我要给你点教训
This hit the spot.
这正好合适
caleb?
I didn't do it.
那不是我干的
Oh,dear.
噢，天哪
well,hey there.
哦，嘿
Hi,karl. Oh!
嗨，karl
Oh,um,quick question--
哦，嗯，一个小问题--
when someone discussesa sensitive situation
当有人向像你这样的律师
with a lawyersuch as yourself,
讲述一件敏感的事情时
when does attorney/clientconfidentiality kick in?
律师委托人之间的保密性 从什么时候开始生效?
From the momentthe lawyer's been hired. Why?
从那律师被雇佣的时刻开始 怎么了?
Here's a check for $100.
这是张一百美金的支票
That's enoughfor a retainer,right?
这足够付律师费了吧，是吗?
Well,I guess.What's going on,bree?
恩，我想是吧 发生什么事了，bree?
My son is tryingto blackmail me.
我的儿子想要勒索我
And I want you to stopthe little S.O.B.
而我想要你去阻止这小杂种
Do you thinkyou could do that?
你认为你能做到吗?
He has an illinois license.
他有一张伊利诺斯州的驾照
It says herehis name is munroe.
上面写着他的名字叫munroe
Does that namemean anything to you?
你对这名字有什么印象吗?
No,but at leasthe wasn't a policeman.
没有，但至少说明他不是个警察
Poor man.
可怜的人
I hope he didn'tsuffer too much.
我希望他没有受太多折磨
mom,are welooking at the same body?
哈哈，妈妈 我们看的是同一具尸体吗?
what is it?
怎么了?
As soon as it gets dark,
一到天黑
we get rid of that body.
我们就处理掉那具尸体
hey.
嘿
Um...
嗯...
I hope it's okay.Carlos let me in.
我希望没有打扰你， carlos让我进来的
Actually,I'm rightin the middle of something,
实际上，我正在做一些事情
and I don't knowwhen I'll be done.
而我不知道什么时候能完成
I'm just here to sayI am sorry,
我只是来说我很抱歉
and I have beena complete idiot.
我是一个十足的笨蛋
all done.
都过去了
so cute.'Cause it's beautiful!
太可爱了 因为它很漂亮!
Is the coast clear?
隔阂被清除了?
Yes,it is.We worked it out.
是的，我们把问题解决了
No kidding.How'd you manage that one?
别开玩笑了，你们是怎么做到的?
Simple. Lynette admittedshe was wrong, and I agreed.
很简单，lynette承认是她的错 而我也那样认为
Well,99% wrong.
嗯，99%是我错
Oh,whatever,close enough.
哦，反正也接近了
Anyway,tom's probably gotdinner ready by now.
好吧 tom可能现在已经准备好晚餐了
So I should get goin'.
我也该走了
Okay.
好吧
Good night.Bye! Mwah!
晚安，bye!
You knowwhat the 1% is,right?
你知道那剩下的1%是什么，对吗?
No,not really.
不，不是很清楚
Does it matter?
那有关系吗?
It kinda does.
是有点关系
I wanna get it clearfor our friendship.
我不想让我们的友情受到影响
Okay.
好吧
What's the 1%?
那1%是什么?
Well,well...
嗯，嗯...
yes,I overreacted.
是的，我是反应过度
I think you can see
我想你能明白
how even thoughI was somewhat off base,
即使我是大错特错了
you were a little wrong,right?
你也有一点错，不是吗?
No. I kissed tom,and it was a harmless joke.
不，我亲了tom 但那是一个无关紧要的玩笑
I think if I had kissedanybody else's husband,
我想如果我亲了别人的丈夫
they would've laughed
她们也会一笑了之
and then forgot about itten seconds later.
然后在十秒钟之后忘了那件事
Okay,let's test that theory.
好吧，让我们测试一下这个理论
See? I don't care.
看到吧，我不在乎
That'S...just a waste of time...
在浪费时间
and spit.
浪费口水
Oh. Okay.
好的
Okay,okay,okay.
好的 好的 好的
Okay! Okay!
好的
I get your point.
完全理解了
All righty,then,my work here is done.
我的任务完成了
Carlos,gaby.
Carlos,gaby
go!
中
Not bad.
不赖
Hey,there he is.
来了
Zach,I'm gladyou could make it.
Zach,很高兴你能来
Hey,zach.
嘿,zach
Mr. Delfino,I didn't knowyou were gonna be here.
Delfino先生, 我不知道你也会来
Yeah,I was just bowling a fewframes and ran into these guys.
是啊，我来玩几局 然后就遇上她们了
I thought I might join you.Is,uh,that okay?
我想我能加入你们，对吧
Yeah,I guess.
我想是的
Oh!
噢
Okay,write that down--nine!
太好了.记下来--9分
Wise guy.
厉害的家伙.
All right,just roll itin there nice and easy.
放松,漂亮地扔出去就行了
Sorry.
抱歉
It's okay.We're still close.
没关系,我们没有输很多
Anyway,julie's totally gonna choke.
反正,julie只会帮倒忙
Just for that,I am notbringing you back a hot dog.
就为了你说的,我不给你带热狗
Zach,do you want one?
Zach,你要吗?
Okay.
好的
You okay?
怎么了?
Yeah,I'm fine,it's just...
我很好,只是...
I don't understandwhat you're doing.
我不明白你们在做什么
What do you mean?
什么意思?
Well,I don't understand whyyou're being so nice to me.
恩, 我不明白你们为什么对我那么好
I mean,I pointed a gunat you guys. You should hate me.
当时我拿枪指着你们 你们应该恨我才对
We don't hate you,zach.
我们不会恨你,zach
You hadan incredibly hard year.
这一年你经历了难以置信的困难
And you shouldn't have donewhat you did,
你做了不该做的事
but we just wannahelp you move on.
我们只是想帮你渡过
Look,um...
听着,恩...
when I was young,
在我年轻的时候
I got mixed upin some really bad stuff.
我干了坏事
I even did some time in prison.
我甚至在监狱呆过一段时间
-Really?
- 真的?
Yeah,but when I got out,
是的,但是当我出来的时候
peoplewere willing to forgive me.
大家都愿意原谅我
Everybody deserves a second chance.
每个人都该有第二次机会
Thanks.
谢谢
You know,I'm gonna go,uh,help julie with the food.
我要过去一下 帮julie一起弄点吃的
So you guys just keep talkingand bowling.
你们尽管聊聊,打打球
Talk and bowl.
聊保龄
Bowl and talk.
保龄聊
Here,let meshow you something.
好了,让我教教你
See the arrowsright in the middle?
对准正中间那条线
Just roll it straight over the one in the center. Okay.
只需要朝中间那个扔过去,可以吗
You don't have to spin itor anything.
你不需要旋转它或其他任何动作
Just right down the middle.
只要对准中间
Look at that!
瞧见了?
Good job.
干得不错!
Hurry up!
快点!
I am hurrying up,okay?
我已经很快了
Wait,no! No! No!
等等,不!不!不!
-What?
- 怎么了?
I dropped the keys.
我掉了钥匙
I don't have 'em.They're in here!
我没钥匙, 在里面
sometimes you just have to laugh.
有时候你只能笑
andrew?
Would you mindturning off your video game?
介意关掉你的游戏机吗?
My lawyer would liketo have a little chat with you.
我的律师想要见你
So even though your mother did witnessgeorge williams' suicide,
即使william自杀时你母亲在场
there's no affirmative dutyto intervene.
也没有义务干预
Therefore,no crime was committed.
因此,不构成犯罪
Even if the police find out,
即使警察发现了
your mom will never seethe inside of a courtroom.
你母亲也不会上法庭
Well,maybe I gotthe story wrong.
这样,也许是我没说清楚
What if she went over thereto help him commit suicide?
如果是她到了那里帮他完成自杀呢?
If you wanna lie to the police,go right ahead.
如果你想要对警察撒谎,尽管去吧
But please knowthat I will sue you.
但是你要明白, 我会起诉你
For what?
为什么?
Abuse of process.
程序滥用
It's when a person triesto exploit the legal system
就是指有些人利用法律程序
for an improper purpose--like blackmail.
以达到非法目的--比如敲诈
You guys can't sue me.I'm just a kid.
你们不能起诉我, 我还未成年
Oh,don't worry.
哦.别担心
I won't start garnishingyour wages until you turn 18.
你满18岁, 我不会削减你的零用钱
Your mom--is she a peach or what?
你妈妈真厉害
If the cops don't give a damn,I'm sure your friends will.
如果警察不在乎 我敢肯定你的朋友们会
How does a littlepublic humiliation sound?
大庭广众之下丢脸, 觉得如何?
Bree,can I geta refill on this?
Bree,能帮我再加点吗?
What are you doing?!
你在干吗?!
Your fatherwas a friend of mine.
你父亲是我的朋友
And if he were around to seewhat a nasty little turd
如果他还在 看到你变成了这么龌龊的垃圾
you've turned into,he'd knock the hell out of you.
他会狠敲你脑袋
Yeah,well,he's not here now,is he?
是的,可他已经不在了,不是吗?
No,he isn't,but if youdon't get your act together
是的,他是不在了 可是如果你不收起你这付嘴脸
and start treating your motherwith some respect,
尊重你的母亲
I'll take careof you myself.
我会亲自教训你
Do you understandwhat I'm saying?
听清楚了?
Yeah.
是的
Good.
很好
Hey,neighbor.
嗨, 邻居
Oh,hey,carlos.
哦.嗨, carlos
Hi.
嗨
I just wanted to thank you forpatching things up with gaby.
我是来谢谢你平息了跟gaby之间的事
Well,sure,no problem.
哦,应该的
It's beenreally tough on her--
她很顽固
everybody finding outabout the affair.
大家都知道外遇了
Yeah,I can imagine.
是的,我能想象
I don't mind telling you,it's,uh...
不介意告诉你,恩...
it's been pretty tough on usthe past couple months.
过去的几个月对我们来说并不好过
Oh,well,I'm not surprised,
哦,我猜到了
and I really,really hopeyou can work it out.
我非常希望你们能度过
Yeah,we're trying.You know...
是的,我在努力.你知道...
mm-hmm? Yeah?
恩~?
Gaby hadan interesting suggestion.
Gaby提了个有趣的建议
Oh?
哦?
She told methat I should go out
她让我出去找人
and have an affairof my own.
搞一次外遇
She thinksit's the only way
这是唯一的办法
I'll be able to get overwhat she did to me
然后我们扯平
and that it just mighthelp our marriage.
这可能会有助于我们的婚姻
Why are youtelling me this?
你为什么对我说这个?
Uh...
恩...
I guess I just,uh...
我想我, 恩...
wanted to know if you hadany thoughts on the subject?
我想知道你是否对这个提议有兴趣?
I... don't.
我...没有
I really don't.
我真的没有
Well,if you ever do,let me know.
好的,如果你有的话,告诉我
By the way...
顺便问一下
mm-hmm?
恩~?
That was one hellof a kiss you gave me.
你给我的那个吻太爽了
You can't fakechemistry like that.
那种感觉绝不是你能装出来的
What the hell is this?
这该死的东西是什么?
Delfino?
Stay away from my son!
离我儿子远点!
oh,my god!
哦,我的天!
dad!
爸爸!
-You okay?
- 你还好吗?
I'm fine.
我没事
Aah!
啊!
so I squirm to avoid hitting his car
我为了绕开他的车打了方向
and I hit parker instead
撞到了停在那里的车子
and that's from the trunk top open
后备箱被撞开
when we got out
我一下车
we found this dead body
就看到这尸体
are you worried now
你现在开始担心了吗?
'cause I am
我有点
not yet
还没
let's be patient, see what will happens
你要耐心点, 看看形势
how'd go
怎么样了?
well I told them everything I know
哦,我告诉了他们我知道的一切
which wasnt much
不太多
so we thinking this is paul
你们觉得是paul?
well he's our friendly neighborhood murderer
他是我们友善的邻居杀手
yes it seems obvious
是的,很明显
I dont know
我不知道
I saw his face when he looked into the trunk
我看到他往车厢里看时的表情
and he looked just as shocked as I was
他跟我一样吃惊
I'm thinking it was the Applewhites
我觉得是Applewhite一家
I talked to the dead guy
我之前跟死者交谈过
He said he was doing appraisal on their house
他说在做Applewhite家的评估
I got a little cheesed
我有点疑惑
so i called all the realtors in town
我问了全城的地产经纪
nobody had even heard of him
没人知道他
that doesnt mean Betty knew him
那并不意味着Betty认识他
please
拜托
those two were fishy
他们是新入住的
they bought that house sightn unseen
看都没看就买了房子
and they did move in the middle of the night
而且他们是午夜搬进来的
and there were noises
还有杂声
what noises
什么杂声
a couple weeks ago
几个星期前
I heard some noises coming
我听到一些来自地下室的杂声
from the basement like cleaning
像是丁丁当当的
I asked betty about it
我问了betty
she lied right to my face
她当着我的面撒谎
what's that about
那是什么?
I dont know
我不知道
now I am worried
现在我开始担心了
Julie
hi
嗨
well my dad found out about us bowling
我父亲发现我们去打过保龄
I cannot be able to do that anytime soon
我最近不能再去了
oh,sorry
哦,抱歉
no no I'm glad we did
不不,我很高兴那样做
I havent felt like a part of a family in a long time
我很久没有感觉像家中的成员了
thanks
多谢
I'd better go back inside
我还是回去了
the act itself never varies
动作是千篇一律的
but each kiss carries a with it a meaning all it's own
但每个吻带着各自的含义
it can convey a husband's eternal devotion
它能传达丈夫永久的专一
or a wife's enormous regret
或妻子莫大的懊悔
it can symbolize a mother's growing concern
它象征母亲日益剧增的担心
or a lover's growing passion
或情人无限的激情
but whatever its meaning
但无论它意味着什么
each kiss
每个吻
reflects a basic human need
反映了人类最基本的一种需求
the needs to connect to another human being
与另一个心灵的交通
this desire is so strong
这种需求如此强烈
it's always amazing when some people
它令人惊讶不已──特别是在那些
dont understand it
不理解它的人眼里
Sync: YTET-gagegao -==www.ydy.com/bbs==-
-=YTET-伊甸园字幕组=- 翻译: 午夜飞行，princeblue 保罗，Noemie，maggiezl
Desperate Housewives Season 02 Episode 01 --END--
-=YTET-伊甸园字幕组=- 校对: dene 时间轴:gagegao